<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2 on Chiu Yu Ko</title>
    <link>/publication_types/2/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2 on Chiu Yu Ko</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/publication_types/2/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Decentralized one-to-many Bargaining (with Duozhe Li), R&amp;R at International Economic Review</title>
      <link>/workingpaper/many-to-one-bargaining/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/workingpaper/many-to-one-bargaining/</guid>
      <description>An industry-wide research joint venture (RJV) does not lead to better technological development or a higher consumer surplus. In contrast, every non-industry-wide RJV leads to strict improvements in both measures. Our results continue to hold when technology transfer is possible. Independent collaboration with technology transfer is an alternative to establishing industry-wide research consortiums.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>From win-win to winner-take-all (with Bo Shen), R&amp;R at Economic Inquiry</title>
      <link>/workingpaper/win-win/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/workingpaper/win-win/</guid>
      <description>An industry-wide research joint venture (RJV) does not lead to better technological development or a higher consumer surplus. In contrast, every non-industry-wide RJV leads to strict improvements in both measures. Our results continue to hold when technology transfer is possible. Independent collaboration with technology transfer is an alternative to establishing industry-wide research consortiums.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research Joint Venture with Technology Transfer</title>
      <link>/publication/rjv-transfer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/rjv-transfer/</guid>
      <description>An industry-wide research joint venture (RJV) does not lead to better technological development or a higher consumer surplus. In contrast, every non-industry-wide RJV leads to strict improvements in both measures. Our results continue to hold when technology transfer is possible. Independent collaboration with technology transfer is an alternative to establishing industry-wide research consortiums.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Technical Analysis with R</title>
      <link>/book/technical-trading-r/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/book/technical-trading-r/</guid>
      <description>This is an introductory textbook that focuses on how to use R to test a technical trading strategy. No prior programming knowledge is needed..</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TikZ Cookbook</title>
      <link>/book/tikz-cookbook/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/book/tikz-cookbook/</guid>
      <description>TikZ is a drawing package in LaTeX. It is very useful to draw a professional-looking diagram. However, the learning curve is a little bit steep for a beginner. This is a cookbook that provides step-by-step illustrations on how to use TikZ to draw various diagrams in economics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TikZ Cookbook Companion</title>
      <link>/book/tikz-cookbook-companion/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/book/tikz-cookbook-companion/</guid>
      <description>TikZ is a drawing package in LaTeX. It is very useful to draw a professional-looking diagram. However, the learning curve is a little bit steep for a beginner. This is a cookbook that provides step-by-step illustrations on how to use TikZ to draw various diagrams in economics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Decentralized mechanisms for river sharing</title>
      <link>/publication/river-sharing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/river-sharing/</guid>
      <description>We study the decentralized implementation of efficient outcomes through multilateral bargaining in the river sharing problem. We consider a class of mechanisms where agents first announce consumption levels and then bargain over monetary compensation. We first determine which mechanisms give incentives to always allocate the water efficiently. Among these, we take an axiomatic approach to single out three mechanisms that guarantee a fair division of the welfare gain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On the Role of Outside Options in Wage Renegotiation</title>
      <link>/publication/outside-option-bargaining/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/outside-option-bargaining/</guid>
      <description>A worker with a superior outside offer starts a wage renegotiation with his current employer. The worker may exercise the outside option whenever a proposal is rejected. Entire surplus may be extracted by the worker. Opting out can arise in equilibrium under complete information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sharing sequential values in a network</title>
      <link>/publication/network-sharing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/network-sharing/</guid>
      <description>We study the decentralized implementation of efficient outcomes through multilateral bargaining in the river sharing problem. We consider a class of mechanisms where agents first announce consumption levels and then bargain over monetary compensation. We first determine which mechanisms give incentives to always allocate the water efficiently. Among these, we take an axiomatic approach to single out three mechanisms that guarantee a fair division of the welfare gain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Note on Budget Constraints and Outside Options in Common Agency</title>
      <link>/publication/common-agency/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/common-agency/</guid>
      <description>In common agency games without budget constraints and outside option, Bernheim and Whinston (1986) show that CPNE=TNE=Principal-optimal core in the payoff space. With budget constraints or outside options, CPNE and TNE may not exist and may not be equivalent to each other. TNEs can be Pareto ranked, contrary to Dixit, Grossman, and Helpman (1996). CPNEs do not avoid a coordination problem, as they can be Pareto dominated by a TNE.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unified China and Divided Europe</title>
      <link>/publication/europe-china/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/europe-china/</guid>
      <description>Severe and unidirectional threat of external invasion fostered political centralization in China. Europe faced a wider variety of smaller external threats and remained politically fragmented. Political centralization in China led to lower taxation and hence faster population growth during peacetime than in Europe. China was relatively fragile in the event of an external invasion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Regional Dependence and Political Centralization in Imperial China</title>
      <link>/publication/dependence-china/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2013 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/dependence-china/</guid>
      <description>Eurasian geography created significant and persistent defense externalities between the Chinese regions. Centralized state is required to enforce cooperation. Building of the national capital in the region where the externality originate. Explain why China’s capitals in strategically important north and west instead of the economically productive south and east.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Choosing a licensee from heterogeneous rivals</title>
      <link>/publication/choosing-rivals/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2013 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/choosing-rivals/</guid>
      <description>Licensing technology to a rival firm when firms have heterogeneous technologies. If a third firm remains in the industry, licensing technology is profitable. Dependent on criteria, chosen licensees are different. Joint-profit- or welfare-maximization, or auction outcomes as a selection criterion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Profit-maximizing Matchmaker</title>
      <link>/publication/matchmaker/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2011 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/matchmaker/</guid>
      <description>Profit-maximizing matchmaker in the many-to-one assignment problem. Consider individualized and package price message spaces as firmsʼ strategy sets. Restricting message space improves resource allocation.  Implementation of the stable correspondence in strong equilibrium.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>