<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Overview on Chiu Yu Ko</title>
    <link>/others/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Overview on Chiu Yu Ko</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/others/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Job Market Tips</title>
      <link>/others/journalfee/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/others/journalfee/</guid>
      <description>This tips is for economic academic job market. This note was prepared based on information adapted from many different sources and experiences of me and others. Now I can no longer tell which part is mine and which part is other. Good luck!
Timeline Job Market Process usually starts from summer until the April the year after.
 Summer: Get approval from advisor September: Final version of paper October: Register for AEA conference and get ready for application November: Send applications December: Schedule and prepare for interviews January: AEA meeting and flyout February-April: Flyout and offers  Summer: Get approval from advisor  Get one main paper ready (Job market paper; JMP) Polish the paper and send it to your committee.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Job Market Tips</title>
      <link>/others/journalranking/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/others/journalranking/</guid>
      <description>This tips is for economic academic job market. This note was prepared based on information adapted from many different sources and experiences of me and others. Now I can no longer tell which part is mine and which part is other. Good luck!
Timeline Job Market Process usually starts from summer until the April the year after.
 Summer: Get approval from advisor September: Final version of paper October: Register for AEA conference and get ready for application November: Send applications December: Schedule and prepare for interviews January: AEA meeting and flyout February-April: Flyout and offers  Summer: Get approval from advisor  Get one main paper ready (Job market paper; JMP) Polish the paper and send it to your committee.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Job Market Tips</title>
      <link>/others/tips/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/others/tips/</guid>
      <description>The following shows the submission fees of various journals in economics and related disciplines. The data is collected in December 2017. The membership is based on the most standard and basic membership for developed countries.
Interesting observation about submission fee by category:
Theory &amp;lt; IO &amp;lt; General Interest &amp;lt; Macro &amp;lt; Finance &amp;lt; Accounting
General Interest On average requires USD100 except QJE (Quarterly Journal of Economics)
   Tier Journal Non-member Member Membership     1 American Economic Review USD200 USD100 USD40   1 Econometrica Must be member Free USD140   1 Journal of Political Economy USD125     1 Quarterly Journal of Economics Free     1 Review of Economic Studies USD100     2 Economic Journal Must be member Free GBP40   2 International Economic Review USD125     2 Journal of the European Economic Association Must be member  EUR75   3 Economics Letters USD65     3 Canadian Journal of Economics Must be member CAD75 CAD50   3 Economic Inquiry USD180 USD120 USD55   3 Economica Free     3 European Economic Review EUR100     4 Oxford Economic Papers - New Series Free     4 Scandinavian Journal of Economics USD100      Theory Almost free.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pedagogy</title>
      <link>/others/pedagogy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/others/pedagogy/</guid>
      <description>GRANT  &amp;ldquo;I hear I forget, I see I remember, I do I understand - Development of large number templates of visual organizers and graphical illustrations&amp;rdquo;
 Teaching Enhancement Grant (TEG), AY2014/2015, National University of Singapore.   TEACHING ARTICLES  Using formative feedback, peer review, and online video-recorded presentations to enhance students&amp;rsquo; research reports. CDTL Brief, 19(1), 3-9. HTML PDF
 Invited Presentation at FASS Teaching Seminar, NUS, 16 Aug 2016.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Supervision</title>
      <link>/others/supervision/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/others/supervision/</guid>
      <description>I am the main advisor of dissertation for two Ph.D. students, and honor thesis for 17 undergraduate students. Besides, between 2015 and 2018, I have been helping Ph.D. students prepare their academic job market.
PHD STUDENTS I am the main advisor for two Ph.D. students, and serve in dissertation committees for four Ph.D. students. I also hosted three visiting Ph.D. students.
Main Advisor  Lu Zhiqi (2019 Expected) Zhang Xuyao (2017, Deputy Director, Asia Competitiveness Institute, Lee Kuen Yew School of Public Policy, National University of Singapore)  Committee Member  Liu Xuyuan (2014, Research Fellow, Risk Management Institute, National University of Singapore) Ding Rong (2015, Assistant Professor, University of International Business and Economics) Liu Bin (2015, Assistant Professor, Chinese University of Hong Kong Shenzhen) Wang Zhe (2017, Post-doc Fellow, Lee Kuen Yew School of Public Policy, National University of Singapore)  Short-term Visting Students  Yujia Cao (Lingnan (University) College, Sun Yat Sen University, 2016-2017) Xu Luyuan (Guangxi University, 2016-2017) Chen Yaqi (Beijing Jiaotong University, 2015-2016)  UNDERGRADUATE I have supervised 20 honor students, 5 independent studies and 2 UROP since 2012.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PhD Conference</title>
      <link>/others/phdconference/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/others/phdconference/</guid>
      <description>I am the coordinator the Second Singapore Economics PhD Conference (2nd SEPC) will be held at the National University of Singapore on 18th November, 2016 (Friday). The first conference (1st SEPC) was organized by the Division of Economics at Nanyang Technological University on 22nd April, 2016. This conference series aims to feature the collective works of Economics PhD students based in Singapore.
For details, please visit https://sites.google.com/site/sgeconphdcon/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reading Group</title>
      <link>/others/readinggroup/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/others/readinggroup/</guid>
      <description>I am currently the coordinator for the reading group. Please email me if you want to be included into the mailing list or present in our workshop.
 Time: Monday 12:00nn-1:00pm Venue: AS2-05-10, National University of Singapore, 1 Arts Link, Singapore 117570  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Service</title>
      <link>/others/service/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2010 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/others/service/</guid>
      <description> Departmental Committee works for the Department of Economics, National University of Singapore:
 Coordinator, Applied Theory and Industrial Organization Workshop, 2013-Present. Co-organizer, Multi-sided Platform Workshop, 2013. Applied Economics Program,2014-2015, 2017-2018. Graduate Program Committee, 2013-2014, 2015-Present. Subcommittee on collaborative programs (double degree programs), 2018-Present.  Professional Ad-hoc referees for:
 Australian Economic Papers Economic Bulletin Economic Record Games and Economic Behavior International Economic Review International Journal of Game Theory Journal of Economic and Behavior Organization Journal of Mathematical Economics Journal of Public Economic Theory Mathematical Social Science Review of Network Economics  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>