<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Chiu Yu Ko</title>
    <link>/r/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Chiu Yu Ko</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>2019</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/r/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Candle Stick</title>
      <link>/r/package/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/r/package/</guid>
      <description>I have developed the following R package to determine candle stick patterns. You can check out more at GitHub.
CandleStickPatternThis package finds common candle stick patterns using daily data (OHLC data).
OverviewThe current version package covers the following patterns:
Doji family (1-day pattern)Doji doji()Dragonfly Doji dragonfly.doji()Gravestone Doji gravestone.doji()Hammer family (2-day pattern)Hammer/Hangman hammer()Inverted Hammer/Shooting Star inverted.hammerEngulfing family (2-day pattern)Bullish Engulfing bullish.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/r/ta-with-r-ch1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/r/ta-with-r-ch1/</guid>
      <description>IntroductionLearning Objectives:
Familiarize with RStudio interface
Use interactive console and code editor
Assignment statement
Hello world
Save R program and R data files
Add comment to your code
Interactive consoleIn the interactive console located at the bottom left window in RStudio, we can see the &amp;gt; symbol. If you type a command and press return, R will evaluate it and print the result for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/r/ta-with-r-ch2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/r/ta-with-r-ch2/</guid>
      <description>Working with DataWe always need to clean data before working. Even data downloaded from the database is not perfect. Sometimes there are missing data. Moreover, when data are from database, we need to combine them before using.
Learning Objectives:
Five basic data types (logical, integer, numeric, complex, character)
Two extended data types (date, factor)
Five basic data structure (vector, matrix, array, data.frame, list)
Basic data management</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/r/ta-with-r-ch3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/r/ta-with-r-ch3/</guid>
      <description>PlottingR is capable of giving very nice graphical plots. We will go over the most popular package ggplot2 for drawing static graphics and dygraphs for dynamic graphs
Learning objectives:
Use ggplot2 to draw basic plots (scatter plot, boxplot, line chart, histogram, frequency polygon, and barchart)
Use ggtheme to improve appearance
Use dygraphs to draw interactive graphs</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/r/ta-with-r-ch4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/r/ta-with-r-ch4/</guid>
      <description>PlottingR is capable of giving very nice graphical plots. We will go over the most popular package ggplot2 for drawing static graphics and dygraphs for dynamic graphs
Learning objectives:
Use ggplot2 to draw basic plots (scatter plot, boxplot, line chart, histogram, frequency polygon, and barchart)
Use ggtheme to improve appearance
Use dygraphs to draw interactive graphs</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/r/ta-with-r-ch5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/r/ta-with-r-ch5/</guid>
      <description>ProgrammingWe will learn basic programming techniques in R to prepare ourselves to write program:
Conditional statementsIterative StatementsLearning Objective:
Learn how to use relational operators
Learn how to use logical operators
Learn how to use conditional statements (if)
Learn how to use basic iterative statements (do while, for)
Learn how to use advanced iterative statements (apply, Reduce)
Logical statementsA logical variable (or Boolean variable) is either 0 (false) or 1 (true).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/r/ta-with-r-ch6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/r/ta-with-r-ch6/</guid>
      <description>ScrappingWe will cover two common ways to extract files that is not from database directly:
pdf files, andhtml files.PDF filesWe will cover how to scrap data from:
extract pdf files stored in offlinedownload pdf file and extractmassive download and extactOffline pdf fileWe need to install and load pdftools package to do the extraction.
install.packages(&amp;quot;pdftools&amp;quot;)library(pdftools)To read pdf as textfile, use pdf_text().</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/r/ta-with-r-ch7/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/r/ta-with-r-ch7/</guid>
      <description>QuantmodQuantmod stands for ``quantitative financial modelling framework’’. It has three main functions:
download data,charting, andtechnical indicator.Then we can conduct simple test on trading strategies. We will learn how to test more complicated strategies.
Before we start, let us use the following code install and load quantmod.
library(quantmod)install.packages(&amp;quot;quantmod&amp;quot;)library(quantmod)Learning Objectives:
Use quantmod package to download stock prices
create chart of stock prices and add technical indicators</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/r/ta-with-r-ch8/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/r/ta-with-r-ch8/</guid>
      <description>QuanstratSince quantstrat is not standard package, we first learn how to install custom package.
We will illustrate the usage of the quantstrat package by showing how four different rules be applied:
naive filter rule,buy and hold,simple SMA rule,SMA rule with a volatility filter.Since the coding is complicated, we first overview the structure of the code. There are five parts:
InitializationIndicator: filter rule/SMA ruleSignals: buy/sell signalsRule: buy or sell?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Financial programming with Excel VBA R</title>
      <link>/r/excel-vba-r/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/r/excel-vba-r/</guid>
      <description>In this book, we learn how to do financial programming in two steps. We first cover Excel that requires minimum programming technique, it is desirable to start learning it first. Excel VBA is covered to provide a smooth transition to more complicated R programming. In particular, students first learn how to use Excel to generate a simple trading system and this builds the foundation for the more complicated trading system in R.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Installation</title>
      <link>/r/installation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/r/installation/</guid>
      <description>Learning Objectives:
 What is R? What is RStudio?
 Install R an RStudio
 Familiarize with RStudio interface
  What is R and RStudio? R is a high-level computer language that is designed for statistics and graphics. One main feature is vector program language like Matlab. It is initially written by Ross Ihaka and Robert Gentleman (hence the name of the software). Currently, it is a free open source software maintained by several contributors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Technical Analysis with R</title>
      <link>/r/ta-with-r/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/r/ta-with-r/</guid>
      <description>I have written an introductory book with R, titled Technical Analysis with R. Readers are prepared how to do
 data manipulation (dyplr package) conduct econometric analysis (regression, time series), plotting (ggplot2 package, dygraphs package), webscrapping (rvest package, wbstat package, quantmod package), and financial analysis (quantmod package, quantstrat package). backtest a complex trading strategy and evaluate the performance.    The book is available through here (this website), bookdown (free online gitbook) or Gumroad (name-your-own-price offline pdf and epub).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Technical analysis with R</title>
      <link>/r/technical-analysis-with-r/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/r/technical-analysis-with-r/</guid>
      <description>I have written an introductory book with R, titled Technical Analysis with R. Readers are prepared how to do
 data manipulation (dyplr package), conduct econometric analysis (regression, time series), plotting (ggplot2 package, dygraphs package), webscrapping (rvest package, wbstat package, quantmod package), and financial analysis (quantmod package, quantstrat package). backtest a complex trading strategy and evaluate the performance.    The book is available through here (this website), bookdown (free online gitbook) or Gumroad (name-your-own-price offline pdf and epub).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>